import { CreateCardDto } from './card.types';

interface IDefaultDeck {
  hiraganaCards: Partial<CreateCardDto>[];
  katakanaCards: Partial<CreateCardDto>[];
  romajiCards: Partial<CreateCardDto>[];
}

export const defaultCardOpts: IDefaultDeck = {
  hiraganaCards: [
    {
      front: 'あ',
      back: 'a',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'い',
      back: 'i',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'う',
      back: 'u',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'え',
      back: 'e',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'お',
      back: 'o',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'か',
      back: 'ka',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'き',
      back: 'ki',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'く',
      back: 'ku',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'け',
      back: 'ke',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'こ',
      back: 'ko',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'さ',
      back: 'sa',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'し',
      back: 'shi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'す',
      back: 'su',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'せ',
      back: 'se',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'そ',
      back: 'so',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'た',
      back: 'ta',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ち',
      back: 'chi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'つ',
      back: 'tsu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'て',
      back: 'te',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'と',
      back: 'to',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'な',
      back: 'na',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'に',
      back: 'ni',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ぬ',
      back: 'nu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ね',
      back: 'ne',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'の',
      back: 'no',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'は',
      back: 'ha',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ひ',
      back: 'hi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ふ',
      back: 'fu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'へ',
      back: 'he',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ほ',
      back: 'ho',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ま',
      back: 'ma',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'み',
      back: 'mi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'む',
      back: 'mu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'め',
      back: 'me',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'も',
      back: 'mo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'や',
      back: 'ya',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ゆ',
      back: 'yu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'よ',
      back: 'yo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ら',
      back: 'ra',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'り',
      back: 'ri',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'る',
      back: 'ru',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'れ',
      back: 're',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ろ',
      back: 'ro',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'わ',
      back: 'wa',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'を',
      back: 'wo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ん',
      back: 'n',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
  ],
  katakanaCards: [
    {
      front: 'ア',
      back: 'a',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'イ',
      back: 'i',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ウ',
      back: 'u',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'エ',
      back: 'e',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'オ',
      back: 'o',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'カ',
      back: 'ka',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'キ',
      back: 'ki',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ク',
      back: 'ku',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ケ',
      back: 'ke',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'コ',
      back: 'ko',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'サ',
      back: 'sa',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'シ',
      back: 'shi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ス',
      back: 'su',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'セ',
      back: 'se',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ソ',
      back: 'so',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'タ',
      back: 'ta',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'チ',
      back: 'chi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ツ',
      back: 'tsu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'テ',
      back: 'te',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ト',
      back: 'to',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ナ',
      back: 'na',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ニ',
      back: 'ni',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヌ',
      back: 'nu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ネ',
      back: 'ne',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ノ',
      back: 'no',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ハ',
      back: 'ha',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヒ',
      back: 'hi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'フ',
      back: 'fu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヘ',
      back: 'he',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ホ',
      back: 'ho',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'マ',
      back: 'ma',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ミ',
      back: 'mi',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ム',
      back: 'mu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'メ',
      back: 'me',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'モ',
      back: 'mo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヤ',
      back: 'ya',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ユ',
      back: 'yu',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヨ',
      back: 'yo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ラ',
      back: 'ra',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'リ',
      back: 'ri',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ル',
      back: 'ru',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'レ',
      back: 're',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ロ',
      back: 'ro',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ワ',
      back: 'wa',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ヲ',
      back: 'wo',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ン',
      back: 'n',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
  ],
  romajiCards: [
    {
      front: 'a',
      back: 'あ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'i',
      back: 'い',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'u',
      back: 'う',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'e',
      back: 'え',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'o',
      back: 'お',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ka',
      back: 'か',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ki',
      back: 'き',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ku',
      back: 'く',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ke',
      back: 'け',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ko',
      back: 'こ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'sa',
      back: 'さ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'shi',
      back: 'し',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'su',
      back: 'す',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'se',
      back: 'せ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'so',
      back: 'そ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ta',
      back: 'た',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'chi',
      back: 'ち',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'tsu',
      back: 'つ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'te',
      back: 'て',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'to',
      back: 'と',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'na',
      back: 'な',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ni',
      back: 'に',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'nu',
      back: 'ぬ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ne',
      back: 'ね',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'no',
      back: 'の',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ha',
      back: 'は',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'hi',
      back: 'ひ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'fu',
      back: 'ふ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'he',
      back: 'へ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ho',
      back: 'ほ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ma',
      back: 'ま',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'mi',
      back: 'み',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'mu',
      back: 'む',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'me',
      back: 'め',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'mo',
      back: 'も',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ya',
      back: 'や',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'yu',
      back: 'ゆ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'yo',
      back: 'よ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ra',
      back: 'ら',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ri',
      back: 'り',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ru',
      back: 'る',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 're',
      back: 'れ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'ro',
      back: 'ろ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'wa',
      back: 'わ',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'wo',
      back: 'を',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      front: 'n',
      back: 'ん',
      lastReviewed: null,
      interval: 1,
      repetitions: 0,
      easeFactor: 2.5,
      __v: 0,
    },
  ],
};
